driverside.com 2019-12-18

# DriverSide Privacy Statement

Privacy

Privacy Statement:

We gather certain types of information about visitors to DriverSide (and its web site DriverSide.com) .  This Privacy Statement governs how we solicit or generate this information and how we use it.  If you have any questions or concerns about anything in this document, please feel free to contact us at [info@driverside.com](mailto:info@driverside.com).  

Your email address

While there is no obligation to register and create a user account with DriverSide, there are a number of reasons why you may decide to do so.  To create an account, you will be asked for to input a valid email address and a password.  Registration is free and doing so enables us to send you important updates on your vehicles.  You always have the ability to change the email address that we store for you and can also request that we delete your email address (and your entire account) anytime by sending such request to [info@driverside.com](mailto:info@driverside.com) or by mailing a request to DriverSide Accounts, 110 Sutter St., Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94104.

To the extent that you do maintain an active email address in our system, we will use commercially recognized and reasonable care to maintain the security of that email address.  We will not share, sell or otherwise make your email address available to any third party unless you request that we do so (described below).  With a registered account on DriverSide, you will be able to request certain email notifications for various content related to your vehicle and/or your experience on DriverSide.   You will also have the ability to list your vehicle(s) for sale and if your choose to do so, you will receive email notifications from DriverSide that there is or are parties interested in the purchase of your vehicle.   You will always have the ability to change or delete any notification requests anytime.

Your Personally Identifiable Information

There are certain optional and voluntary services available on DriverSide that will require you to provide personally identifiable information (e.g., your name, your address, your e-mail address, your telephone number) in order to receive the benefit of those services.  Some of the services that would require submission of personally identifiable information include, but are not limited to, your request for a price quote or proposal for goods and/or services from a local service provider, local automobile dealer, or from an automotive manufacturer.    **This personally identifiable information will be shared between us and those companies in order to deliver the information that you request.   In some cases, in order to deliver those services, you personally identifiable information may also be disclosed to other entities who work with us or those companies to fulfill your request.   While DriverSide.com cannot control, and is not responsible for, the manner in which any of such companies and other entities use such information, we will always use commercially reasonable means to ensure the security of your information and mandate that the use of such information be limited to your specific request for information.**

In certain locations on DriverSide in which we obtain personally identifiable information from you, we may include "check boxes" for the purpose of soliciting your consent to receive special offers and/or other information from us and other entities selected by us. By leaving these check boxes "checked," you are choosing to receive commercial communications from us and/or those other entities. In that event, you will have the opportunity at any time to "opt-out" of receiving future commercial communications from us (on behalf of itself and/or such third parties) either  by sending a request to us through our [info@driverside.com](mailto:info@driverside.com)  or by sending us a request by mail to DriverSide Accounts, 110 Sutter St., Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94104.

Access to Your Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you would like to delete any of your personally identifiable information, you may correct, update or delete it by either sending a request to us at [info@driverside.com](mailto:info@driverside.com) or by sending us a request by mail at DriverSide Accounts, 110 Sutter St., Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94104.

Your Vehicle Profile Pages

A feature included in your voluntary DriverSide account is the ability to establish and customize individual profiles for any number of vehicles.  Each of the profiles that you create can contain whatever information you choose to include.  Those profiles can be made public on the DriverSide site, and in such case, the profiles, including any information that decide to add the profiles, will be accessible by other visitors to DriverSide.  DriverSide will not publish any personally identifiable information on these profiles, and in fact, has no mechanism to do unless you decide to add such information at your sole discretion.  When setting up your vehicle profile of DriverSide, you will be given the opportunity to decide whether the entire profile, certain parts of it, or none of it are made public.  Such choices can be modified by you at any time through your account settings, by sending a request to [info@driverside.com](mailto:info@driverside.com) or by sending us a request by mail at DriverSide Accounts, 110 Sutter St., Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94104.

Your Zip Code

We request your Zip Code in a number of locations on the DriverSide site.  Providing us your Zip Code enables us to display to you various content and tools relevant to your specific location.  We provide this information for Zip Codes that are within one of the 50 states or the District of Columbia, but not those in other U.S. territories or possessions or for the postal codes of Canada or other countries.

When you first provide your Zip Code to us **** in response to a direct request by us that you provide your Zip Code, we serve a "cookie" to you that includes your Zip Code. ("Cookies" are described below.) That cookie permits us to recognize your Zip Code when you use other applications, or upon your return to DriverSide without our having to ask you again for your Zip Code.

You have the opportunity to change your Zip Code at appropriate times during your visit to DriverSide  if you want to get information for a different Zip Code.  Changing your Zip Code in any part of the DriverSide site automatically updates your Zip Code cookie.

Other Cookies

"Cookies" are small data files that many Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file contains information such as a user ID that a site may use to track the pages you've visited. However, the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Cookies served by us don't permit us to read data from your hard drive or to read cookie files created by other Web sites.

We use cookies in many ways, including the following:

First Visits: When you first visited the DriverSide, we served a cookie to you. This cookie resides permanently on your hard drive (unless you chose to delete it) and enables us to track visitor activity across our Web sites.

Features: Whenever you use certain features on the DriverSide site, such as Dealer Locator, we may serve a "session cookie" to you, which is a cookie that is only used by us during your use of that application. In addition, for some applications we may serve a cookie to you that has a longer expiration date. These cookies help us manage our delivery to you of feature information and related content.

Lead Forms: In certain other features, you may be presented with a form that requests, among other items, your name and contact information. When this form is submitted by you the information you provide is stored on our computers, so that we have a record of what we have sent to our partners. We also serve a cookie to you telling us where that information is maintained, so that we can "pre-fill" your name and contact information for you when in the future you call up a similar form.

Please note that we do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our the DriverSide site.

Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, please contact us at [info@driverside.com](mailto:info@driverside.com) or by sending a request by mail to DriverSide Accounts, 110 Sutter St., Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94104.

Our Community Features

DriverSide provides a number of means by which you may communicate with other visitors and with us. Many of these are the various communication and personalization tools and services that are part of our "community. The community features include, but are limited to, Question and Answer features and other features that solicit your review of automobiles and/or related service providers.

In order to add content to DriverSide through these community features, you must first become a member of the DriverSide agree to our Terms of Use.  (You do not need to register in order to browse or read the content provided by our members.) The Terms of Use set forth a number of information sharing and disclosure practices for our community features, and accordingly supplements this Privacy Statement.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or allow such persons to become members of the DriverSide.. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register as a member or send any information about yourself to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us through either at [info@driverside.com](mailto:info@driverside.com) or by sending a request or notification to DriverSide Accounts, 110 Sutter St., Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94104.

Surveys

Occasionally, we conduct visitor surveys to better target our content to our audience or for the benefit of third parties with whom we do business. Accordingly, sometimes the aggregate survey results are shared with our advertisers and partners. We never share any survey information about specific response with any third party unless that individual consents.

Share my profile

Setting up a vehicle profile includes a feature that permits registered users to electronically forward that profile to someone else by clicking on a link. The sender must provide his or her e-mail address, as well as that of the recipient. The sender's information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the page. Neither the sender's information nor the recipient's information is used for any other purpose.

Links to Other Web Sites

The DriverSide site contains links to many other Web sites not operated by us, including sites where you can obtain automotive products and services. However, this Privacy Policy only applies to the DriverSide and the information we collect, and we are not responsible for the privacy polices or practices of any other Web sites.

Changes to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the DriverSide site means you accept those changes.
